https://www.fmfcu.org/privacy-policy/

Effective date: March 27, 2019
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.fmfcu.org website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined in this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy, terms used in this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.fmfcu.org
Definitions
Service
Service is the https://www.fmfcu.org website operated by Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union
Personal Data
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
Usage Data
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
Data Controller
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed.
For the purpose of this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.
Data Processors (or Service Providers)
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.
We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.
Data Subject (or User)
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.
Information Collection and Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer support
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
To monitor the usage of our Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union may process your Personal Data because:
We need to perform a contract with you
You have given us permission to do so
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
To comply with the law
Retention of Data
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Data
Business Transaction
If Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.
Disclosure for Law Enforcement
Under certain circumstances, Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).
Legal Requirements
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
“Do Not Track” Signals
We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.
You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.
Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.
If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union relied on your consent to process your personal information.
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this FMFCU Web Site Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By phone number: 484.259.1000
By mail: 5 Hillman Drive, Suite 100, Chadds Ford, PA 19317
FMFCU MEMBER PRIVACY POLICY
WHAT DOES FRANKLIN MINT FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why? Financial companies choose how they share Your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires Us to tell You how We collect, share, and protect Your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what We do.
What? The types of personal information We collect and share depend on the product or service You have with Us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
account balances and payment history
credit history and credit scoresHow?
How? All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, We list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information, the reasons Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether You can limit this sharing.
[[["Reasons We Share Your Personal Information","Does the Credit Union share?","Can You limit this sharing?"],["For Our everyday business purposes - such as to process Your transactions, maintain Your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus","Yes","No"],["For Our marketing purposes - to offer Our products and services to You","Yes","No"],["For joint marketing with other financial companies","Yes","No"],["For Our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about Your transactions and experiences","Yes","No"],["For Our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about Your creditworthiness","No","WE DON'T SHARE"],["For Our affiliates to market to You","No","WE DON'T SHARE"],["For non-affiliates to market to You","No","WE DON'T SHARE"]],[{"row":0,"col":0,"visualRow":0,"visualCol":0,"prop":0,"borders":{"className":"border_row0col0","border":{"width":1,"color":"#000","cornerVisible":false},"row":0,"col":0,"top":{"hide":true},"right":{"hide":true},"bottom":{"hide":true},"left":{"hide":true}},"jtcellstyle":{"font-weight":"bold"}},{"row":0,"col":1,"visualRow":0,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter","jtcellstyle":{"font-weight":"bold"}},{"row":0,"col":2,"visualRow":0,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter","jtcellstyle":{"font-weight":"bold"}},{"row":1,"col":0,"visualRow":4,"visualCol":0,"prop":0,"jtcellstyle":{"font-weight":"inherit"}},{"row":1,"col":1,"visualRow":4,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":1,"col":2,"visualRow":4,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":2,"col":0,"visualRow":5,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":2,"col":1,"visualRow":5,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":2,"col":2,"visualRow":5,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":3,"col":0,"visualRow":6,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":3,"col":1,"visualRow":6,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":3,"col":2,"visualRow":6,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":4,"col":0,"visualRow":7,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":4,"col":1,"visualRow":7,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":4,"col":2,"visualRow":7,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":5,"col":0,"visualRow":1,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":5,"col":1,"visualRow":1,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":5,"col":2,"visualRow":1,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":6,"col":0,"visualRow":2,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":6,"col":1,"visualRow":2,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":6,"col":2,"visualRow":2,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":7,"col":0,"visualRow":3,"visualCol":0,"prop":0},{"row":7,"col":1,"visualRow":3,"visualCol":1,"prop":1,"className":"htCenter"},{"row":7,"col":2,"visualRow":3,"visualCol":2,"prop":2,"className":"htCenter"}],[{"row":0,"col":0,"top":{"hide":true},"right":{"hide":true},"bottom":{"hide":true},"left":{"hide":true},"border":{"width":1,"color":"#000","cornerVisible":false}}],[]][]Reasons We Share Your Personal InformationDoes the Credit Union share?Can You limit this sharing?For Our everyday business purposes - such as to process Your transactions, maintain Your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor Our marketing purposes - to offer Our products and services to YouYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor Our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about Your transactions and experiencesYesNoFor Our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about Your creditworthinessNoWE DON'T SHAREFor Our affiliates to market to YouNoWE DON'T SHAREFor non-affiliates to market to YouNoWE DON'T SHARE
How does Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect Your personal information from unauthorized access and use, We use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect Your personal information, for example, when You
open an account or make deposits or withdrawals from Your account
apply for a loan or show Your driver’s license
use Your credit or debit card
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives You the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about Your creditworthiness
affiliates from using Your information to market to You
sharing for non-affiliates to market to You
State laws and individual companies may give You additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates – Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include financial companies such as State Financial Network, LLC., CU Settlement, and CU Realty Services.
Non-Affiliates – Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to You.
Joint Marketing – A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to You.
Our joint marketing partners include categories of companies, such as: credit card companies, financial service providers and insurance companies.
Rev. June 2018
Please click here for the pdf version of our privacy policy.
Questions?  Call (610) 325-5100 or (800) 220-3193 or write to Us at:
Privacy Compliance Officer
Franklin Mint Federal Credit Union
5 Hillman Drive, Suite 100
Chadds Ford, PA 19317-9998
Schedule an Appointment
We use cookies to ensure we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue using this site, we will assume you agree with our cookie settings.OkNoRead more
